Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of War and Peace Movements Serials TAM.757
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Shundahai Network News: Shundahai Network, Salt Lake City, UT, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 31)
- SNAFU: Newsletter for Military Personnel, Families, and Veterans: Support Network for Armed Forces Union, New York, NY, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- So What Does No Business as Usual Do Besides Take to the Streets?: NBAU, San Francisco, CA, Undated (Box 11, Folder 32)
- SOA Watch Update: SOA Watch, Columbus, GA, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 33)
- Social Science Handbook: Island Press, New York, NY, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 34)
- Soldier of Fortune: Omega Group Ltd., Boulder, CO, 1976-1980 (Box 11, Folder 35)
- Solidarity!: American Committee for Solidarity with the Vietnamese People, San Francisco, CA, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- South Manhattan Peace and Freedom Report: Peace and Freedom Party, New York, NY, Undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
- South West Agitator: London Agitator, London, UK, Undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Souvenir Journal: Armistice Day Celebration: Armistice Day Celebration Committee, Los Angeles, CA, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Speakers Backgrounder: FREEZE, Undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Spew: War Resisters League, New York, NY, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Spoke & Word: Bikes Not Bombs, Roxbury, MA, 2002-2003 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- SPU Bulletin: Student Peace Union, Chicago, IL, 1962-1964 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Star Light: A Way Out of the Arms Race: Jack Kidd / Star Light, Earlysville, VA, Undated (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Star Wars: First Strike Against the World: Coalition Against the Space Arms Race, San Francisco, CA, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Star Wars and the State of Our Souls: The Whole Earth Papers Global Education Associates, East Orange, NJ, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Stop Star Wars Now!: Women's Peace Proxy, Washington, DC, Undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Strategic Hamlet: Isla Vista, CA, Undated (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Strategy for Peace ... Conference Report: Stanley Foundation, Warrenton, VA, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Student Action: Campus Crusade for Christ Inc., San Bernadino, CA, Undated (Box 24, Folder 12)
- Student Mobilization Committee Position Paper: Student Mobilization Committee, New York, NY, Undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Student Mobilizer: Student Mobilization Committee, New York, NY, 1968-1972 (Box 12, Folder 13, Box 18, Folder 9-10, Box 23, Folder 14-16)
- Student Mobilizer: Student Mobilization Committee, Washington, DC, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 14, Box 23, Folder 17, Box Shared Tamiment 052, Folder 19)
- Student Mobilizer: Student Mobilization Committee, Chicago, IL, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Student Peace Union Bulletin: Student Peace Union, Chicago, IL, 1961-1962 (Box 12, Folder 15-16)
- Student Worker: Freedom Now Press, Washington, DC, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- Supplement: Pittsburgh Committee for a Comprehensive Peace in the Middle East, Pittsburgh, PA, Undated (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Suppose Britain Loses: Committee to Defend America by Aiding the Allies, New York, NY, Undated (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Survival network Newsletter: Survival Network Information Center, New Orleans, LA, Undated (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Survivalfest 84: Mobilization for Peace and Justice, New York, NY, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Synapse: Neahtawanta Research and Eduaction Center, Traverse City, MI, 1990-1991 (Box 24, Folder 19)
- Teach Peace: Peace Education Committee, Teaneck, NJ, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Telegram: US Committee Against Militarization, Chicago, IL, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Test Banner: American Peace Test Clearinghouse, Salem, OR, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- The Professional: Professionals' Coalition for Nuclear Arms Control, Washington, DC, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- They Forgot God: Henry H. Klein, New York, NY, 1941 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Thinkpeace: San Francisco Study Group for Peace & Disarmament, San Francisco, CA, 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Thoi Bao Ga: U.S. Committee to Aid the National Liberation Front of South Vietnam, Cambridge, MA, 1972-1973 (Box 12, Folder 25-26)
- Tien Phong Avant Garde: Montreal, Quebec, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Tikkun: Campaign for Peace and Democracy/East and West, New York, NY, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- To All Members of the Performing Arts Community...: Performing Artists for Nuclear Disarmament, New York, NY, Undated (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Tools for Peace and Justice: Oxfam America, Boston, MA, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 30)
- Torch: Revolutionary Socialist League, New York, NY, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Toward a World Disarmed: Committee for World Development and World Disarmament, New York, NY, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 31)
- Towards the Peoples' Congress: World Council of Peace, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 32)
- Two... Three... Many: Committee of Returned Volunteers, Chicago, IL, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 33-34, Box 28, Folder 6)
- U.S. Out of Korea: Youth Against War & Facism, New York, NY, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 35, Box 28, Folder 7)
- Ukranian Peace News: Ukranian Peace Committee, London, UK, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Unconventional News: Miami Conventions Coalition, Miami, FL, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Uncovering the Hidden Draft: CCCO Annual Report 1985: CCCO / A National Agency for Military and Draft Counseling, Philadelphia, PA (Box 12, Folder 36)
- Undercurrent News: Draft Resisters, Buffalo, NY, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- UNDO News: Union for National Draft Opposition, Princeton, NJ, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 37, Box 25, Folder 6)
- United States Anti-Imperialist League: United States Anti-Imperialist League, Oakland, CA, Undated (Box 25, Folder 7)
- University Press Service Release: University Press Service, Philadelphia, PA, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 38)
- US Navy Films for the Public: Office of Information Department of the Navy, Washington, DC, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 39)
- USO News Service: USO, New York, NY, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 40)
- V.I.A. Voice: Veterans of Industry of America, Oklahoma City, OK, 1934 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Valley War Bulletin: American Friends Service Committee, Florence, MA, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- VDC News: Berkeley VDC, Berkeley, CA, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Verdict: Student Mobilization Committee, New York, NY, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 41)
- Veteran / Vietnam Veterans Against the War/Winter Soldier Organization: VVAW/WSO, Chicago, IL, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Veterans for Peace Journal: Veterans for Peace, Portland, ME, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 42)
- Via Pacis: Des Moines Catholic Worker Community, Des Moines, IA, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Victor: Committee for Cultural Relations with Foreign Countries, Hanoi, Vietnam, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 43)
- Viet Nam: Peoples Press, San Francisco, CA, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 44)
- Viet Nam: Production Unity of the Instituto del Libro, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Viet Nam News & Reports: Montreal, Quebec, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Viet Nam Pictorial: Hanoi, Vietnam, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Viet Nam: Whose Victory? Whose Defeat?: Peoples Press, San Francisco, CA, Undated (Box 25, Folder 15)
- Viet/Nam Bulletin, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Vietnam: Congress of People's Representatives for the Formation of the Provisional Revolutionary Government of the Republic of South Viet Nam, Hanoi, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Vietnam: Le Bao, Vietnam, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Vietnam: Lee Hong Minh, New Delhi, India, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Vietnam: Comite Vietnam National, Paris, France, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Vietnam - Defeat U.S. Imperialism!: Progressive Labor Party, Brooklyn, NY, Undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Vietnam - People's War or Negotiations?: Progressive Labor Party, Brooklyn, NY, Undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Vietnam America Friendship Week: Friendship Week Office, Cambridge, MA, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 16)
- Vietnam Courier: U.S. Committee to Aid the N.L.F.-S.V., New York, NY, 1966-1967 (Box 25, Folder 17)
- Vietnam Generation: Vietnam Generation, Inc., Silver Spring, MD, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Vietnam Information Bulletin: Vietnam News Agency, Rangoon, Burma, 1966-1972 (Box 13, Folder 9-18, Box 14, Folder 1-9, Box 28, Folder 8)
- Vietnam International: International Confederation for Disarmament and Peace, Paris, France, 1973-1975 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Vietnam News & Reports: Vietnam News & Reports, Montreal, Quebec, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 18-21)
- Vietnam News Bulletin: Vietnam News Agency, Rangoon, Vietnam, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 9-10)
- Vietnam RDVN (Photos d'Actualites): Xunhasaba, Hanoi, Vietnam, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Vietnam Report: Union of Vietnamese in Canada, Montreal, Quebec, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 22-23)
- Vietnam Vets Say Prevent WWIII: Vietnam Veterans United to Prevent World War III, New York, NY, Undated (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Vietnam: The Struggle for Peace: Indochina Peace Campaign, Santa Monica, CA, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Vietnamese View of Human Nature: Indochina Peace Campaign, Santa Monica, CA, Undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Visit to an Air Force Hospital: The War-Wounded Come Home: Liberation News Service, New York, NY, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 24)
- Vista: Radio for Peace International, Portland, OR, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Voices for Peace: America-Israel Council for Israeli-Palestinian Peace, Downers Grove, IL, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Voices from Prague: END Palach Press Limited, London, UK, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Volkischer Beobaehter: National Socialist German Worker's Party, Germany, 1953 (Box Shared Tamiment 052, Folder 20)
- Walking Point: San Francisco Vietnam Veterans Project, CA, Undated (Box 15, Folder 14)
- War & Peace Digest: War and Peace Foundation, New York, NY, 1991-2001 (Box 15, Folder 15-16)
- War Bulletin: War Bulletin, Berkeley, CA, 1972-1973 (Box 26, Folder 1-3)
- War in the Darkness: Andre Girard, France, 1944 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- War News: Warren Hinckle, New York, NY, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- War Resister: War Resisters League, New York, NY, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 18, Box 28, Folder 11)
- War Watch: Out Now, Salinas, CA, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- war/peace: Center of War/Peace studies of New York Friends Group, New York, NY, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- WarReport: Bulletin of the Institute of War & Peace Reporting: Institute for War & Peace Reporting, London, UK, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Warsaw Accuses: Polish Embassy, New York, NY, 1945 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Washington Peace Center Newsletter: Washington Peace Center, Washington, DC, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Washington Peace Letter: Washington Peace Center, Washington, DC, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- What Are You Going to Do About It?: Harper & Brothers, New York, NY, 1936 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- What is Vietnam Veterans Against the War-Winter Soldier Organization: Vietnam Veterans Against the War/Winter Soldier Organization, Chicago, IL, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Women Strike for Peace Newsletter: Women Strike for Peace, New York, NY, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Women Under Torture: Indochina Peace Campaign, Santa Monica, CA, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Women's International League for Peace and Freedom Newsletter: Women's International League for Peace and Freedom, New York Metropolitan Branch, New York, NY, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Word of Mouth: Word of Mouth, Jacksonville, FL, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Working Together: The Bay Area Nonviolent Community, San Francisco, CA, Undated (Box 28, Folder 12)
- World Conference to End the Arms Race for Disarmanent and Detente: World Peace Council, Helsinki, Finland, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- World Congress of Peace Forces: International Preparatory Committee, Moscow, Russia, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- World for Peace and Democracy: National Executive Committee, New York, NY, 1939 (Box Shared Tamiment 052, Folder 21)
- World Peace Congress Bulletin: World Peace Congress, Paris, France, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- World Peace Council Assorted Newsletters: World Peace Council, 1973-1974 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- World Peace Council List of Members: Information Center of the World Peace Council, Helsinki, Finland, 1977-1980 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- World Peace News: American Movement for World Government, New York, NY, 1985-1992 (Box 26, Folder 8-9)
- World Review In Defence of Peace / In Defence of Peace: The Bureau of the Committee of the World Congress of the Defenders of Peace, Paris, France, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- World Veteran: World Veterans Federation, Paris, France, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- World War 3 Report: Shadow Press, Brooklyn, NY, 2004 (Box 16, Folder 13, Box 28)
- Yalta: Ou le Partage du Monde: Robert Laffont, Paris, France, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Yank: The Army Weekly: Branch Office, Army Education and Information Division, War Department, New York, NY, 1944 (Box 26, Folder 10-12)
- Youth in the World War: Youth Publishers, New York, NY, Undated (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Zivilcourage: Zivilcourage, Frankfurt, Germany, 2009 (Box 16, Folder 16)